Morning.
Hi.
Oh, how was your
date last night?
Pretty good.
Oh, good.
( screams )
Oh, my God. Sorry.
Okay. Really good.
Anyway, I've got to go.
I'm late for work.
You're going to leave
this person with me?
Hey, don't worry.
She's a terrific girl.
And hey, listen.
You do me a favor?
When she comes out,
could you just mention
that I'm not looking for
a serious relationship?
That'd be great.
Whoa! What, are you kidding?
Just casually slip
it in, you know?
Lay the groundwork.
Tell her... I'm a loner.
No, an outlaw.
She doesn't want to
get mixed up with
the likes of me.
You know what, that's
a lot to remember.
Can't I just tell her
that you're a pig?
Hey, I'm going to
call her later myself.
Honest.
Look, come on, Chandler
used to do it.
He'd even make
the girl pancakes.
Plus he'd make extras
and leave them for me.
Well, forget it, I'm not telling
that girl anything.
That is not my responsibility.
Fine.
Now, where did we land
on those pancakes?
Get out.
Hi.
Sorry about that
but I couldn't get that lock
to work on the door.
Yeah, Joey kind of disabled it
when I moved in.
You must be Rachel, I'm Erin.
Hi.
I don't mean this to sound
like high school
but did he say
anything about me?
Would you like
some pancakes?
Yeah.
♪ So no one told you
life was gonna be this way ♪
♪ Your job's a joke,
you're broke ♪
♪ Your love life's D.O.A. ♪
♪ It's like you're always
stuck in second gear ♪
♪ When it hasn't been
your day, your week ♪
♪ Your month,
or even your year ♪
♪ But I'll be there for you ♪
♪ 'Cause you're there
for me, too. ♪
Come on, why
are we here?
Okay, okay,
take a guess.
The hot chicks.
Okay, okay, I was
typing names into
the library computer
earlier, you know,
you know, for fun...
and I typed mine
in and, uh, guess
what came up?
My doctoral dissertation.
It's here.
Yeah, it's right down here
in the biggest library
in the university.
Wow, that's actually
pretty cool.
Yeah. Oh, um...
There's also a book here by
a woman named Wendy Bagina.
( ecstatic moaning )
What is that?
Sounds like two people
are really enjoying
the Dewey decimal system.
We're so sorry.
Excuse us.
You didn't bring me here
to do that, did you?
She sent the chicken back again?
She said it's too dry now,
and she wants to come back here
and explain to
you exactly how
she wants it.
Hmm... Well, fine, I'd like
to meet this chicken expert.
Send the Colonel in.
Oh...
my... God!
Lucky bastard!
Janice!
How are you...
Miss Hot Shot Chef
at the big, fancy restaurant
with the best chicken ever?
( laughs )
I'm fine.
Oh, what is that
on your finger?
I'm blind.
Oh, uh...
So? Who's the lucky guy?
Oh... my... God!
I am so sorry, sweetie.
Are you okay?
You didn't tell her we're
getting married, did you?
Well, she saw the ring.
Did she freak out?
Well, she was shocked
when I told her
but, then again,
so were most people.
Right.
She actually has a boyfriend,
you know, herself.
Name's Clark.
Uh, she also kind of invited
herself to our wedding.
Clark, too.
You said no, right?
Huh?
Well, she cornered me, I mean...
she asked me if the wedding
was in town.
I mean, what was I
supposed to do?
Lie.
How hard is that?
Your check's in the mail.
Oh, your baby is so cute.
I can't wait
to read your book, Ross.
So she'll
come to the wedding.
Maybe it won't be so bad.
What, do you think she's just
going to sit there quietly?
You don't think she's going
to want to make a toast?
You don't think she's going to
want to grab the microphone
and sing "Part-time Lover"?
Oh, my God!
She's not going to like
the chicken
that night either,
is she?
You know what?
It's going to be okay.
She's probably not going
to even want to come.
Really?
No, that was a lie.
See how easy that was?
So, so...
You would have just lied?
Yes.
It would have really
been that easy?
Yes.
Good, so do it
Saturday night
'cause we're going to
dinner with her and Clark.
( giggles )
Hey, what's up?
Hey!
Oh, hey, who's your friend?
Hey, Joey.
Erin, you're still here.
Yeah, we ended up spending
the day together
and had such a great time.
Why wouldn't you?
Erin is great.
And then there's you guys.
Well, listen, I'd
better get going.
Today was great, thanks.
I know.
Okay.
And Joey...
Last night was fun.
Yeah.
I'll, uh, I'll call you.
Oh, and I'll call you, too.
Or I'll call you.
And call me.
Okay.
Okay, good to
see you again.
Bye.
Bye-bye.
Rachel:
Bye.
So, system kind
of broke down, huh?
Oh, Joey, I'm sorry.
I just couldn't tell her
all those things you
wanted me to tell her.
And, you know, we
got to talking, and...
We want you to marry her.
What?
She is so amazing,
you have no idea.
No idea? Who do you
think brought her here?
Cupid.
Joey, she's so cool.
She speaks four languages.
Man, do you know
what guys want!
No, Joey, come on.
She's so perfect for you.
I mean, she's sweet, she,
she likes baseball...
and she, she had two beers
at lunch.
My beers?
Look, you guys, she's a very
nice girl, okay?
We had a good time.
But I just... I don't see it
going anywhere.
Yeah, but you
always say that.
Yeah, maybe if you gave
this girl a chance
it would go somewhere.
Look, I'm sorry, you guys.
I just don't think so.
Whatever.
Fine.
Hey, don't start judging me.
Huh? You're the one who's
in love with her assistant, huh?
And you, you're the one
who's having the affair
with the guy who keeps
the pigeons on the roof.
Phoebe!
Secret affair.
People are doing it
in front of my book.
I'm sorry?
My doctoral dissertation
is in the library at school.
I went to see it, and there were
students making babies...
right in the middle
of the paleontology section.
Oh, my God! Did you get
to see anything good?
Let me ask you something.
At your school, was there, like,
a place on campus
where students went to,
to fool around?
Yeah, there was.
In the corner of the library
where all these dusty books were
that nobody ever read,
yes, there was.
Great, 'cause people
kept showing up.
I think it's like a thing.
Wait, hold on a second.
Fifth floor, against
that back wall?
Oh, for crying out loud!
All right, so we should
go catch our movie.
Well, now, what's the rush?
I like to see the previews.
The candy.
Oh, hey.
Well, look who's here.
Hey, Joey.
Hey, Erin.
Hey, Rachel.
Hi.
Well, we were just
about to take off
and see a movie.
Yeah.
Oh.
Oh, no.
What's wrong?
Oh, Phoebe, we forgot
that party we have to go to.
Oh, no.
What party?
A birthday party.
Oh, whose birthday party?
Both:
Allison's birthday party.
Oh? And how old is Allison?
Both:
Thirty-two.
Wait a minute...
Why don't you
guys do something?
Yeah, look how
that worked out.
Excuse me?
Hi. I'm a professor here.
Do you know
the Paleontology section
fifth floor, stack 437?
Well, yes.
Just give me five minutes.
I just have to find someone
to cover my shift.
No, no, no.
Can I speak to someone
in charge, please?
How can I help you?
Hi. I was wondering,
is it possible
to increase security
in the Paleontology section?
See, I-I wrote a book
that's up there
and instead of reading it,
people are-are...
well, they're rolling around
in front of it.
We are aware of the problem
you're referring to.
But as far as increasing
security, I'm afraid the library
is very understaffed.
I-I can't help you.
Well, fine. Fine.
If-if I'm the only person
with, uh, any
appreciation
of the sanctity
of the written word,
then I'll go up there
and defend it myself.
And don't you follow me.
Hey.
Oh, hey.
How did it go with Erin?
Oh, unbelievable.
We had the best time.
Yeah!
Oh, so you're not
mad at us anymore?
No. no. no.
You guys were totally right.
This was so much better
than the first time we went out.
That was so awkward.
We were both really nervous.
Didn't you sleep together?
Yeah. That really calms me down.
And... we have so much
in common.
She-she loves sandwiches.
Sports... although,
she is a Met fan.
Not much of an issue now,
but if were ever to have kids...
Oh, my God!
Listen to you
talking about
having kids.
Oh.
Oh, my Joey.
Oh!
Please don't get married
before I do.
Oh.
Okay?
Oh. I just
cannot believe that Clark
stood me up.
He may still show up.
Oh, what are you, stupid?
It's been three hours!
Is that all?
Let's just go on
to happier things, okay?
Um, why don't you tell me
about your lovely wedding?
Well, actually, uh,
there was something
that we wanted to tell you
about the wedding, um...
( clears throat )
It's going to be
a-a small ceremony.
Uh, tiny.
We're not even sure
why we're having it.
It's actually going
to be just family.
Oh... wait.
You two think of me as family?
Oh, I have to ask you
something now, and be honest.
Do you want me to sing
"Careless Whisper"
or "Lady in Red"?
How can you say that?
The Mets have no closer.
What about Benitez?
What about game one
of the series?
What about, shut up?
You shut up.
I love arguing with her.
I'll be right back.
Okay.
So, how's it going
with Joey?
Uh... okay.
Okay?
Wait, okay.
Tell me
that you like him, please?
I mean, tell me
that you like him.
Look, he's a really great guy,
and I know
that you really want this
to work out
but... I just don't see
this having a future.
What?
But you said
that you liked him.
I mean, what happened?
Did you just
change your mind?
Kind of.
Then change it back!
I'm sorry.
I... it's just,
there's no real spark.
No spark?
Didn't you sleep together?
Yeah.
Uh, tramp!
Does Joey have any idea?
I really don't
think he does.
And you know what?
Maybe you guys
could help clue him in.
You know, tell him
I'm not interested
in a serious relationship
or something.
Yeah. You mean, like, that
you're kind of a loner?
Yeah. That'd be great.
Yeah, and maybe that
you're a real stronzo.
I'm sorry?
Well, I guess Italian
isn't one of the four
languages you speak.
Hey... want to go?
Yeah, let's go.
Okay. See you guys later.
Bye, guys.
See ya.
Hey, thank you so much.
Wow!
Well, I guess it wasn't Cupid
that brought her here.
No. Just regular
old flying dwarf.
Yes? Yes?
How can I help you?
Uh, we were just
looking around.
Oh. Oh. You're-you're
fellow scholars.
What exactly were
you looking for? Hmm?
Perhaps, uh...
Perhaps... Dr. Chester
Stock's musings
on the Smilodon
Californicus?
Uh...
"Uh, uh..."
Get out of here!
Hi. Meeting someone?
Or-or are you just
here to brush up
on Merriam's views
on evolution?
Actually, I find Merriam's views
far too progressionist.
I find Merriam's views
I'm sorry.
Who are you?
I'm a professor here.
Uh, Ross Geller.
Ross Geller?
Why do I know that name?
It's a... wait.
Did you write this?
Yes.
You're the person
who checked out my book?
You know, you look nothing
like I would have thought.
You're-you're so young.
Well, I, uh... I
skipped fourth grade.
Uh-huh.
I am very, very sorry.
Hey.
Hi.
So how was
your date?
Oh, it was great.
I mean, we walked
all around the village.
We-we went to
this ice cream place
split a milk shake.
70-30, but still.
And guess what?
I'm thinking of
taking her upstate
to one of those
bed and breakfasts.
She said she wants
to go away with you?
No, no, no, no, no.
It's a surprise,
but it's going to be tricky
because she's going to be
pretty busy at work for a while.
Oh, yeah.
Hey, Joey-Joey, look, honey,
we-we need to talk, okay?
Um...
I kind of got the feeling
from her today
that, uh...
that she's not looking
for a serious relationship.
Where are you
getting this?
Well, she told me.
She said she's kind of a loner.
Oh.
Joey...
Hey, Rach, it's
cool, you know?
I'm a loner, too, right?
Hey, Joey.
You know what?
You are way
too good for her.
Yeah, and I promise,
next time I will
just say good-bye
and tell them you are not
looking for a relationship.
No.
No. Don't do that.
Just...
Next time, make sure
she really likes me.
Well, that, too.
Joey?
Yeah.
Do you want
some pancakes?
Finally.
Okay.
What are we going to do?
I say we go with
"Careless Whisper."
( knocking )
Chandler?
Did she see us yet?
Did she see us?
Janice, what are you
doing here?
Well, um...
I thought I was going
to go back to my apartment
but then I just felt like
I really couldn't be alone
tonight.
I was just wondering if I could
maybe stay here with you.
Just, I really feel like I need
to be with family.
Our kids are going to call her
Aunt Janice, aren't they?
Please?
It's just otherwise, I really
don't know what I might do.
Aren't you just a
teensy bit curious?
Ah! Do you have any tissues?
In the bathroom.
Okay.
Just... just let her stay.
No, no, no, no, no.
If we let her stay,
she will stay forever.
Kind of like your
Barcalounger.
Is that what you're
thinking of right now?
I never stop
thinking about it.
Hey, you guys?
Do either one of you
want to get in there
before I take my bath?
Janice, I'm sorry, but, uh...
( clears throat )
you can't stay here tonight.
Why not?
Honestly?
Our apartment is a hotbed
for electromagnetic activity.
Now, Monica and I
have been immunized
but, sadly, you have not.
( guffawing )
Okay, I'm going
to need a comforter
but do you have
a hypo-allergenic one?
Because otherwise
I get very nasal.
( honks )
Do you have a cat?
'Cause it's already
happening.
( honks )
You hear that? Listen.
( honking )
( honking angrily )
Oh, my God!
You have to go!
Why?
Because Chandler
still has feelings for you.
He does?!
Say again?
That's right.
And that is why you
can't stay here tonight
and probably why you shouldn't
come to the wedding.
Feelings.
Such strong feelings.
I mean...
I realize that his
feelings may never
completely go away...
but you can.
Oh... my God.
I understand.
I'm so sorry.
I'll go.
Good-bye, Monica.
I wish you a lifetime
of happiness with him.
Chandler...
You call me when this
goes in the pooper.
Don't sweat it.
I got this
section covered.
Yeah, in fact, I got
this little baby
to shine in people's eye...
okay, see you later.
I just wanted to show
Monica your book.